adsoptimal.com 2017-06-13

# Monetize your web traffic on mobile today - AdsOptimal

## Privacy Policy

Social Nation, Inc. (DBA AdsOptimal, OmniVirt, VrOptimal) is committed to protecting consumer privacy and to clearly informing users about the collection and use of information when using our services. As a result, we have put together this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect and use certain information. This Privacy Policy applies to AdsOptimal Service´s mobile advertising products and services (our “Service”), as well as our company websites located at [www.adsoptimal.com](http://www.adsoptimal.com/), [www.omnivirt.com](http://www.omnivirt.com/), and [www.vroptimal.com](http://www.vroptimal.com/) (“VrOptimal”) , (collectively, “AdsOptimal Service” or our “Websites”).

**Website Data Collection**

AdsOptimal Service is the sole owner of the information collected on our Websites. The information may consist of both Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”), and is collected in order to conduct business with current and prospective business clients. We do not sell or rent data collected via our Websites to other parties, but we may provide it to third-parties as necessary to conduct our business operations and for the performance of our Services with our customers. AdsOptimal Service collects this data and uses it to provide requested information to prospective clients, to establish self-service advertiser and publisher accounts, and otherwise as necessary to conduct our business.

Our Websites may contain links to other websites, such as sites providing news coverage of the company, to partner sites for case studies, and to industry association sites of which AdsOptimal Service is a member. AdsOptimal Service is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third-party websites.

**Our Business**

AdsOptimal Service is a mobile advertising company. We use our proprietary technology to offer advertising solutions to our clients, which includes working with advertisers to deliver their advertising campaigns across our network of mobile publishers and application (“app”) developers (our “Platform”).

**Data Collected On Our Platform**

AdsOptimal Service collects data from across its Platform. This data, which may include anonymous identifiers associated with your mobile device, does not identify you personally, and may come from such sources like your mobile web browser, or the apps that you use. We use this Non-PII along with our technology to perform a variety of tasks, such as limiting the number of times a specific advertisement is presented to the same mobile device (frequency capping), providing an advertisement to only certain types of mobile devices, or providing a report to a client on the number of its advertisements that were clicked. We may share this Non-PII with clients, vendors, and other companies that we conduct business with. We may also use some of this data to provide interest-based advertising, as discussed more fully below.

**Interest-Based Advertising and Opt Out**

AdsOptimal Service works with its clients to provide ads that are likely to be more interesting and more relevant to mobile device users. One way we do this is by using our technology, along with Non-PII related to your mobile device that is gathered across different sources. Examples of this data, which does not identify you personally (Non-PII), may include things like mobile websites you have visited or mobile apps that you use, preferences that you may have provided to your app provider or to AdsOptimal Service (as in a survey), or location information. We refer to this as interest-based advertising.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from our website and stored on your computer’s hard drive. You have the ability of deleting cookies on your computer should you so wish (See Opt-Out).

The Site uses browser cookies to record current session information. If you choose the ‘remember me’ option, you are issued a permanent cookie. A permanent cookie is one that remains on the hard drive after the browser application has been closed. AdsOptimal Service use browser cookies for ad frequency throttling and User counting. AdsOptimal Service browser cookies do not track users outside of AdsOptimal Service. AdsOptimal Service does not share any cookie information with third parties.

**Opt-Out Of Cookies**

You can choose to remove cookies stored by us from your computer, or to prevent us from storing cookies on your computer in the first place. AdsOptimal Service cookies will appear in your browser. Most browsers are set to automatically accept cookies. However, most modern browsers can also be configured to decline cookies, and allow you to delete existing cookies. Consult your browser’s documentation, typically available through the “Help” menu on the toolbar, for instructions on how to prevent the browser from accepting new cookies, how to delete cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use or access some of the interactive features offered on the Site or by some AdsOptimal Service. For assistance with removing cookies or limiting communications from us, please email us at contact@omnivirt.com.

**Device-Based Opt-Out for Mobile Applications**

For Android devices, you may signal your desire to “opt-out of interest-based ads” through your device settings. For iOS devices, you may signal your desire to “limit ad tracking” through your device settings. If you enable this device-based preference, Airpush will still serve ads, but no longer serve interest-based ads to the device where you exercised this choice.

**Third-Party Websites**

We may provide ads that link to third-party sites, third-party apps or other third-party content (“Third-Party Content”). This Privacy Policy does not extend to Third-Party Content, or any services offered on Third-Party Content.

**Data Collection On Behalf Of Third-Parties**

We may, on behalf of our clients, collect information from end users. This may occur, for example, if someone submits information in response to an ad that we provide on behalf of an advertising client. Such information may consist of PII, non-PII, or both. In such situations, we collect the information and provide it to our client, and it will be subject to such client’s privacy practices.

**Children´s Privacy**

AdsOptimal Service is very sensitive to the issue of children´s privacy. AdsOptimal Service´s websites, products, and services are not developed for, or directed at, children under the age of 13. If you believe your child has provided AdsOptimal Service with personally identifiable data, or registered at one of AdsOptimal Service´s websites, and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us using the contact info below.

**Security**

AdsOptimal Service takes steps to protect the security of information that we collect. To that end, we have designed and deployed hardware, software, and networking solutions in an effort to reasonably secure and protect access to our systems and data.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may need to disclose information, including PII, when in our good-faith judgment we are required to do so by law, or when such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process. We may also transfer all or some of the data discussed in this policy, in connection with a corporate merger, acquisition, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

AdsOptimal Service is committed to continually examining and reviewing its privacy practices, and may make changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any changes that we believe are material are made to the company´s privacy practices, we will post a revised Privacy Policy on this website.

**Questions and Concerns:**

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, you may contact us:

Social Nation, Inc.  
Phone: (415) 993-VR-AD  
Email: [contact@omnivirt.com](mailto:contact@omnivirt.com)

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 5, 2016**
